{
    "id": "b5a950fc8eb7405faadac1fb24bd2553",
    "title": "Sentence Correction Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My father knows how to teach English .............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6092fca4bd24c1ab2a054c5e269f477"
        },
        {
            "question": "We want a new house to ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "live in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4874f9535f5f4cdda5306de80b80c030"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................................... for you since 9 oâ€™clock in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am waiting",
                "have been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5fcd8f988d2e4739bf81a91820f1c48e"
        },
        {
            "question": "James ..................................... suffering from fever since yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e73b77f19f0e401b9f1f9994b2e6c759"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither Ann nor Mary .................................... arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1ba336a03cd94833960eac79ff48b30a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call on you before I .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "will leave"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "95960fa1427e4a1ba8cc272124f77c2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................................... all the books to the library yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "have returned"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0be73fc1c62f4a2aa19e1ad2238e2f24"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each man and each woman ...................................... the right to vote.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a113634d79b44ee98f9dea5e39da2733"
        },
        {
            "question": "Walking along the road, the old man was .............................. by a bus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ran over",
                "run over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39dc6ee78a644c78a6a4dea5c1910350"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................................... hard for the last two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is studying",
                "was studying",
                "has been studying"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "118a5473ed6041b690dd3c7ef2f01492"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not used ...................................... in busy streets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to drive",
                "driving",
                "to driving"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "523b5f486a7a46e99c4b5d05de83e528"
        },
        {
            "question": "The poet and dramatist ....................................... dead.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4cb291f54af40a28b25ed4bd72ed996"
        }
    ]
}